take Southeast Asia as
an right now and
I think it's pretty
absurd I'm show this
to you is that
if individuals are earning
money now and
they're using Buy Pay
Later to buy things
online and then they're
it on not very
productive things It's not
like they're buying maybe
you buy a MacBook
and you do podcasts
on your MacBook and
you make money with
that that's great That's
productive spending It's like
la boos and it
nailed it So there's
a of like non
productive spending So I'll
use like a say
on TikTok shop right
So I spoke to
a lot of people
who are involved in
that ecosystem and saying
that okay what are
people buying And then
a of it are
not actually productive stuff
They're like perfumes or
they're like and so
there's just like stuff
you don't actually need
So they don't fully
make you they don't
influence your Yeah
Yeah yeah yeah The
ROI is not great
The ROI is not
great That is terrible
right It's Yeah it's
terrible right So what
has Buy Pay Later
done And what has
like what has credit
cards you done for
the US back then
you And so I
think they they inject
a lot of they
help the because they
inject loss spending Yeah
So